RAJ MANDLOI

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Passionate about developing user-friendly software applications. Capable of working in a team environment or working independently. I continually seek new challenges and desire to expand my knowledge and experience. Capability to explore, learn and understand new business domains and new technology.





8770265192



Indore, Madhya Pradesh



rajmandloi1232@gmail.com



https://raj-mandloii.github.io



www.linkedin.com/raj-mandloi



github.com/Raj-Mandloii

SKILLS

- React
- Nodejs
- React Native
 - Express
- Redux
- Mongo DB Firebase
- Javascript
- Typescript
- HTML
- CSS
- Flutter
- Dart

in soft skills.

Apprenticeship, Masai School

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Created 25+ mini projects and 5+ MERN Stack projects. Tech stack: Javascript, React.js, Nodejs, MongoDB

FLUTTER DEVELOPER

Saturncube Technologies

Ahmedabad, Gujrat

• Check-Me (Health Checking) App.

• Business Listing App.

Bengaluru, Karnataka

09/2021 - 02/2022

03/2022 - 02/2023

Designed and developed a mobile app for significant clients, Collaborated with a team of developers and project managers to meet client deadlines and deliver a high-quality product on time and within budget. Some of the work are as follows:

Spend 1200+ hours in coding and 400+ hours in Data structures and algorithms and 100+ hours

- Intix 2.0 App.
- Lotto Ticket Scanning App.
- Sports Recording App Taggy
- Tech stack: Flutter, Dart, GetX, Rest APIs.

PROJECTS

E-Commerce Website



View Live



Source Code

E-Commerce is a shopping website built using React, Redux, and Nodejs. React handles the dynamic rendering of product listings, search and filtering, and shopping carts.

• Features - Product catalog, Shopping cart, sort, search, and filters.

Tech stack: React, Redux, Redux-Thunk Chakra UI, Node.js, Mongo DB.

Whatsapp Web - Clone



Wiew Live



Source Code

A WhatsApp Web clone built using React, Socket.io, and Node.js is a real-time communication application that mimics the functionality of the popular messaging platform.

• Features - User Authentication, Real-time messaging, and status.

Tech stack: React, Axios, Node.js, Socket.io, Mongo DB.

Hub Spot Website - Clone



View Live



Source Code

This is a clone of the HubSpot CRM Website, mainly focused on User Interface and User Authentication.

• Features - User Authentication, Service pages

Tech stack: React, Redux, Redux-thunk, Axios, Chakra UI.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Masai School

03-2022 - 02-2023

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE

Vikram University

03-2019 - 03/2022